<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Open Academic Environment Podcast</title>
        <link>http://oaeproject.org/</link>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&#x2117; &amp; &#xA9; 2016 Apereo Foundation Open Academic Environment</copyright>
        <itunes:subtitle>Uncovering impactful connections between technology and education in building an academic network of collaboration, discussion and feedback</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Apereo OAE</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Higher Ed interview series and discussion panel with authority figures from educational technology, academic research, university management, policy makers to educators and instructors</itunes:summary>
        <description>The OAE Podcast is an interview series and discussion panel where we talk to authority figures within higher education about technology, academic research, university management, policy makers to educators and instructors</description>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>OAE Project</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>oaeproject@gmail.com</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:image href="http://oaeproject.org/assets/img/podcast/oaeproject-podcast-art.png" />
        <itunes:category text="Education">
            <itunes:category text="Education Technology" />
        </itunes:category>
        <item>
            <title>Innovation within Institutional IT</title>
            <itunes:author>Apereo OAE</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>Nicolaas Matthijs talks to us about building IT innovation within a higher education context</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>We celebrate our inaugural episode by talking to Nicolaas Matthijs, the Project Lead for the Apereo Foundation’s Open Academic Environment Project and an entrepreneur, Full Stack developer, Open Source contributor and Educational Technology enthusiast with significant experience on all sides of the EdTech fence. He is someone who continually pushes the barriers when it comes to technology for higher education. Nicolaas shares his perspectives on the challenges, innovations and where he sees technology best serving the eco-system of learning, research and collaboration for Universities in the modern world. Follow Nicolaas at @nicolaasm and join the conversation through oaeproject.org or @OAEProject on Twitter.</itunes:summary>
            <enclosure url="http://oaeproject.org/podcast/oae-podcast-ep01.mp3" length="325252" type="audio/mp3" />
            <guid>http://oaeproject.org/podcast/oae-podcast-ep01.mp3</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <itunes:duration>00:28:14</itunes:duration>
        </item>
        <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
        <atom:link href="http://oaeproject.org/podcast/podcast.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    </channel>
</rss>
